https://www.gameindustry.com/privacy-statement/

Privacy Statement of Game Industry News
Information about our Organization and Web site
Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organization like Game Industry News. We are based in the USA.Our principal activity is: Web-Based MediaOur privacy policy covers Game Industry News and its Web site:
Organisation Name:
Game Industry News
Address:
City:
Monck’s Corner
State:
SC
Country:
USA
Controller:
Nate Wooley
Web Sites(s):
www.gameindustry.com
Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access
You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data.
The services and links of our Web site
Our Web site does not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others.
Our Web site does not include links to third party Web service providers.
Automatic Collection of Information
We do not use cookies on our Web site.
We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals.
Data Collection and Purpose Specification
We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services.
We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations.
To access the table of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used, please click here
We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated in the table below.
Children’s Privacy
We do not knowingly collect personal data from children.
Additionally, to ensure that children’s privacy is respected on our Web site, we:
do not distribute personal data, nor allow subscribers to communicate with one another.
Disclosure and Visitor Choice
We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organizations.
Confidentiality / Security
We do not give visitors to our Web site the option of using a secure transmission method to send us their personal data.
We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:
unauthorised access
improper use or disclosure
unauthorised modification
unlawful destruction or accidental loss
All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors’ personal data.
We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.
Access to the personal data we may hold about you
You can ask us, by:
sending an email (publisher@gameindustry.com)
whether we are keeping personal data about you.
Upon request, which you can indicate by:
sending an email (publisher@gameindustry.com)
We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, within a month, although we may before require proof of your identity. We will provide the information without any charge.
We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data:
erased
rectified or amended
completed
We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal.
We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.
Privacy Compliance
There are no national laws or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organization.
There are no global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organization.
In order to demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with any applicable privacy instrument, we are:
voluntarily committed to a Self Assessment procedure
Self Assessment procedure
Name or designation of the privacy policy person or service
Greg Crowe
URL
www.gameindustry.com
Address
8228 Red Wing Ct., Frederick, MD 21701
Country
USA
Privacy Support
If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact:
Name/designation :
Nate Wooley
Department :
Publisher
Email address :
publisher@gameindustry.com
URL :
www.gameindustry.com
We do not recommend another means by which visitors’ concerns may be addressed.
TABLE of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used
Primary personal data/Business information
x
volunteered by each visitor
–
not collected
Primary personal data
Technical administration of the Web site
Research &development
–
Police/Justice data such as civil/criminal actions brought by or against the visitor
–
–
–
–
–
Hot Stories
Latest
Popular
Cloudpunk Brings Compelling Sci-fi Adventure to Consoles
Bookish Wednesday: Vainqueur the Dragon by Maxime Durand
Cyberpunk 2077 Gets Launch Trailer
THQ Nordic Bringing Four Games To Stadia
Darkkin Queen Book Takes Series in New Direction
Ghost of Tsushima – The Japan Feudal Game We’ve All Been Waiting For
Today
Week
Month
All
6 Best Fan Service Anime Video Games
5 best gambling games you can play at home
Best Video Games of 2020
In Loving Memory: GiN Founding Publisher Nate Wooley
EVE Online Now Fully Localized for Japan
Best Slot Games to Play On Your Mobile in 2020
News and Industry HappeningsCyberpunk 2077 Gets Launch TrailerTHQ Nordic Bringing Four Games To StadiaGhost of Tsushima – The Japan Feudal Game We’ve All Been Waiting ForBest Video Games of 20205 Reasons Why You Should Play Online CasinoEVE Online Now Fully Localized for JapanWRC 9 Racing Game Gets Free Content Update, New Cars20 Years Later: How Bet365 Became the World’s Most Popular Betting SiteLonely Mountains Downhill Gets Free Steam DemoMotherboard Game Presents Tron-like Inner-Computer WorldHow is Online Poker Different from At-the-Table GamesCuisine Royale Shooter Transforms into CRSED: F.O.A.D.Commandos 2 Gets Remastered for Nintendo SwitchWhat is the Safest Way to Buy WoW Gold Classic?MORE...
Your Free Daily News Source Of The Video Game Industry
Search for:
